<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sharad Shriram</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sharad Shriram</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 14:09:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Sharad</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 14:09:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently working with the Centre for Networked Intelligence at the Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India. Prior to my current position, I completed my masters in Computer Science (August 2019) with a specialization in Data Science and Technology from the Web Information Systems group, at the Delft University of Technology under the supervision of Prof. Dr. ir. Alessandro Bozzon. I hold a B.Tech. in Computer Science and Engineering from Amrita University, Coimbatore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:52:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Page to be updated
Thesis  Master Thesis: &amp;ldquo;A Human-Machine Approach to Preserve Privacy in Image Analysis Crowdsourcing Tasks&amp;quot;, TU Delft (2019).  Peer-reviewed articles Combining Internet of Things and Predictive Analytics  Sharad S, Sivakumar PB, Ananthanarayanan V. An automated system to mitigate loss of life at unmanned level crossings. Procedia computer science. 2016 Jan 1;92:404-9. Sharad S, Sivakumar PB, Narayanan VA. The smart bus for a smart city—A real-time implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:52:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>This page will house all the projects that I have worked on! This page is currently under construction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firstpost from Hugo</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/2020-02-27-firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:13:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/2020-02-27-firstpost/</guid>
      <description>Hi!!
If you are stopping by this page, it&amp;rsquo;s really nice of you to drop by, Thank you!
It has been a while, like a few years, since I wanted to write and maintain a blog. I had spent close these few years thinking, scribbling and rethinking of what I would want to write about, while my vocabulary witnessed a gradual degradation in the context of an operating system.
In those four years, I had been building some awesome things, mostly as part of my courserwork but now that I think about them, I lost most of my notes working on them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>