<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sharad Shriram</title>
    <link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sharad Shriram</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sharadshriram.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Activities</title>
      <link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/activities/</guid>
      <description>Teaching  Teaching Assistant, Delft University of Technology  Web Science and Engineering, a graduate course offered in the first period at Faculty of Electrical Engineering, Mathematics and Computer Science (Sep 2018 - Jan2019) Digital Skills, a pilot course to make first-year bachelor students in non-CS programs learn programming in Python (Sep 2018 - Jan2019)    Talks  &amp;ldquo;Working with real-time location data in your IoT projects&amp;rdquo;, Amrita University, Coimbatore, 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy dabbling on code, some towards a large projects while others are explorations of new tools - they are open-sourced and can be found on Github. I hope to update my blog with learning experiences for these projects as and when time permits
Featured Project  An city-scale agent-based simulator to compare different intervention strategies during an epidemic: Code on Github A hybrid human-machine approach to preserve privacy in images: Code - coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://sharadshriram.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sharadshriram.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>My current research interests are broadly in the topics of Human-centered AI, Natural Language Processing, Edge Intelligence, and Data-driven Modelling.
This page has a few selected outcomes of ongoing and older research. You can always find the current research outcomes on Google Scholar
 Master Thesis: &amp;ldquo;A Human-Machine Approach to Preserve Privacy in Image Analysis Crowdsourcing Tasks&amp;rdquo;, TU Delft (2019).
 Manuscripts and Technical Reports  P Parag, P Patil, S Shriram, R Sundaresan, H Tyagi, N K.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>