<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-19T15:30:12+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sharad Shriram</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">The infinite loop - website upgrade</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2020/12/19/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The infinite loop - website upgrade" /><published>2020-12-19T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-12-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2020/12/19/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2020/12/19/update.html">&lt;p&gt;I have been playing with different frameworks and static site generators to build my dream website.
The past builds of the website ranged from a static, one-page website developed using different HTML/CSS theme to the previous build which was developed on Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-upgrade&quot;&gt;The upgrade&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After many failed attempts to tweak the base theme of the previous build, I found myself coming back to use Jekyll. I have been using Jekyll for different projects and even had some test builds for my website using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://mmistakes.github.io/minimal-mistakes/&quot;&gt;minimal-mistakes&lt;/a&gt; theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always like the website themes that were created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://html5up.net/&quot;&gt;ajlkn&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://html5up.net/&quot;&gt;https://html5up.net/&lt;/a&gt;. Instead of using a theme directly in its native HTML/CSS falvor, I wanted to find themes in Jekyll that were ports of  &lt;a href=&quot;https://html5up.net/&quot;&gt;https://html5up.net/&lt;/a&gt; themes. I stumbled upon this theme, called &lt;a href=&quot;https://html5up.net/read-only&quot;&gt;ReadOnly&lt;/a&gt; which was ported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/digitaladapt/&quot;&gt;digitaladapt&lt;/a&gt;. This port became the base for my new website build. This time, I spent some time getting familiar with the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Liquid&lt;/code&gt; templating language that Jekyll uses to tweak this theme for this current build.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all on the website upgrade. I think I will be sticking to this build for a while.. (&lt;em&gt;fingers crossed!&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;blog-plans&quot;&gt;Blog plans&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan for this blog is to make it a sort of development/ research journal where I note down things I learn or come across.
While the current plan of the blog is mostly intended for journalling purposes, I hope it can help some one later who might be working on a similar topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blog’s name &lt;em&gt;Random rambles&lt;/em&gt; as it sounds will also be about things I find interesting, like productivity hacks and living with less along with an occassional cooking experiment. So, if the built up to this blog was made as a technical one.. the answer is that it will be me rambling about random things I stumble upon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till next time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">I have been playing with different frameworks and static site generators to build my dream website. The past builds of the website ranged from a static, one-page website developed using different HTML/CSS theme to the previous build which was developed on Hugo. The upgrade After many failed attempts to tweak the base theme of the previous build, I found myself coming back to use Jekyll. I have been using Jekyll for different projects and even had some test builds for my website using the minimal-mistakes theme. I have always like the website themes that were created by ajlkn on https://html5up.net/. Instead of using a theme directly in its native HTML/CSS falvor, I wanted to find themes in Jekyll that were ports of https://html5up.net/ themes. I stumbled upon this theme, called ReadOnly which was ported by digitaladapt. This port became the base for my new website build. This time, I spent some time getting familiar with the Liquid templating language that Jekyll uses to tweak this theme for this current build. That’s all on the website upgrade. I think I will be sticking to this build for a while.. (fingers crossed!). Blog plans The plan for this blog is to make it a sort of development/ research journal where I note down things I learn or come across. While the current plan of the blog is mostly intended for journalling purposes, I hope it can help some one later who might be working on a similar topic. The blog’s name Random rambles as it sounds will also be about things I find interesting, like productivity hacks and living with less along with an occassional cooking experiment. So, if the built up to this blog was made as a technical one.. the answer is that it will be me rambling about random things I stumble upon. Till next time.</summary></entry></feed>